logoguru.co.uk 2009-04-04

# UK Logo Design By LogoGuru.co.uk

---  
Privacy Policy  
LogoGuru.co.uk Privacy Statement  
At [**LogoGuru.co.uk**](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/), we are dedicated to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The information we ask you for is only so that we can process your order effectively and in an efficient way. [**LogoGuru.co.uk**](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/) will at no point in time share your personal and private information with any third party outside of our company without your explicit consent. We use 128-bit SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption to ensure that your information is kept private and is protected at all times  
LogoGuru.co.uk Confidentiality  
At [**LogoGuru.co.uk**](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/), all your contact information such as your name, postal and e-mail addresses and telephone number is considered private and confidential. This information is saved in a secure location and is accessible by select staff members only. Also the information you give us will be used exclusively to process your order.

We at [**LogoGuru.co.uk**](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/) guarantee that none of your personal information will be shared with any third party, individual or organization without your prior authorization or consent. We consider personal information to be all the information that can be used to contact or locate you, or determine your identity.  
  
LogoGuru.co.uk Information Collection  
At [**LogoGuru.co.uk**](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/), we employ various methods by which we gather user data. This information is protected by our privacy policy and will not be issued to any persons or organizations without your approval.   
  
  * When you register to use our services, we require your basic personal information which includes your name, company name, mailing address, email address, phone and fax numbers
  * We also collect your necessary billing information such as your credit card number, the type of card you use, its expiration date, your billing address and your Credit Card Validation Code or CVV2. This information is then verified through VeriSign.
  * Additionally, we retain information that can be of a personal nature. This information voluntarily given by you includes opinions concerning complaints, appreciations and comments given on our products/services. 

Non-Disclosure of Information   
At [**LogoGuru.co.uk**](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/), we will not disclose or reveal your personal information to any unaffiliated third party without your approval. If we wish to release your personal information, we will seek your consent to do so, explaining clearly the information we seek to disclose, the purpose of disclosing the information as well as to whom we wish to reveal this information to.  
  
However, there are limited circumstances in which we may disclose your personal information such as

  * We may disclose information in special cases such as to contact or bring legal action against a person who is causing injury, or interference, consciously or unconsciously, with the rights and/or property of **[LogoGuru.co.uk](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/)** or other visitors to this website.
  * We may also disclose information if required to do so by the law, court order, or other government or legal entities. However, we will attempt to notify you before we do so, if permitted by law. 

Removal or Altering of Information  
As general information tracking is essentially anonymous, we at [**LogoGuru.co.uk**](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/) have no means by which to trace this data that is gather by the use of our service.   
  
**Security**

  * We at **[LogoGuru.co.uk](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/) **use the latest security and encryption methods to thwart any unauthorized access and preserve data accuracy. 
  * Your personal information is stored in our database behind a firewall for additional security. The server is protected by security 24x7 at a secure third party site.
  * We at **[LogoGuru.co.uk](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/) **cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to us over any wireless network or the internet, as no data transmission is guaranteed secure. As a result, you do so at your own risk. 
  * We at **[LogoGuru.co.uk](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/) **do not encrypt your regular web sessions on your website. 

**LogoGuru.co.uk Privacy Policy Changes**  
  
We at **[LogoGuru.co.uk](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/) **reserve the right to change our privacy policy at anytime. However, all changes will be made subsequent to your notification via email prior to the policy alterations. [**LogoGuru.co.uk**](http://www.logoguru.co.uk/) **** is not liable for the privacy policies of its various affiliate programs.
